#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/erika-l-a2a12762 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Character Designs
Augmented Reality (AR)
After Effects

### **Publications**

British Gas-Explorer

# Erika L.

AR @ Meta Reality Labs - Avatars

Cupertino, California, United States

## Summary

Currently, Product design lead for AR experiences for avatars on XR headsets and mobile. Developing the latest technologies and creative tools for user experiences that bring avatars to life and open up the metaverse to the masses.

www.erika-lee.com

## Experience

Meta

AR @ Meta Reality Labs - Avatars March 2022 - Present (1 year 2 months)

스노우 SNOW Corporation Creative Director - ZEPETO April 2021 - January 2022 (10 months)

Instagram AR Designer May 2018 - April 2021 (3 years) San Francisco Bay Area

At IG, I have the unique opportunity to work at the intersection of bleeding edge AR & creative tools and the massive scale and distribution of the Instagram platform. I create high-quality interactive experiences, partnering with industry leading Engineers, Creative Technologists, 3D Artists, Product Designers, Product Managers, and Researchers on a daily basis.

Buck
Freelance Designer
March 2018 - March 2018 (1 month)
Los Angeles, California

Psyop Freelance Designer November 2017 - February 2018 (4 months)

Greater Los Angeles Area

Created concept art and style frames for ongoing advertisement campaigns and pitches.

Charlex

Freelance Designer

June 2017 - October 2017 (5 months)

Greater New York City Area

Presented and executed ideas and designs while collaborating with client and director for Vitafusion campaign for web and digital ads.

My Active Driveway Freelance Designer April 2017 - May 2017 (2 months)

Greater New York City Area

Developed creative solutions for Clash of Clans advertising campaign while successfully communicating design ideas and collaborating with creative team.

Big Star Motion Design Freelance Designer May 2016 - March 2017 (11 months) Greater New York City Area

Delivered designs for projects including digital and print graphic campaigns, rebrands, documentary infographics, various broadcast promos for clients such as National Geographic, I Heart Radio, TNT, Project Runway Jr.. Helped build long-term client relationships who repeatedly returned for creative

services.

The Honest Company
Freelance Designer
March 2016 - April 2016 (2 months)

loyalkaspar Freelance Designer January 2016 - February 2016 (2 months)

Executed creative solutions for a wide range of projects from television branding, commercials, and graphic campaigns. Helped establish look and feel for rebrand of ESPN College Football and Mike&Mike. Additional projects

include, SyFy's The Expanse, CNN The Eighties and Sixties, Rangers, and Epix.

**Imaginary Forces** 

Matte Painter

November 2015 - November 2015 (1 month)

Collaborated with 3D department, creative directors, and designers to help design concept art for Dolby Pre-Show, as well as executed matte paintings for HBO Game of Thrones teaser and The Masters tournament ipad app.

Psyop

Freelance Designer

June 2015 - August 2015 (3 months)

Greater New York City Area

Worked directly with creative directors and the 3D team to execute character designs and prop/environment concept art for animation based commercials.

Imaginary Forces
Freelance Designer/Matte painter
April 2015 - April 2015 (1 month)
New York, NY

Nickelodeon - UK, Australia, CEE, Israel, Russia, Ukraine & Baltics Freelance Designer September 2014 - November 2014 (3 months)

ocpicinoci zo i+ i ivovcinoci zo i+

New York, NY

Developed designs for 2015 Kids Choice Awards and on air commercial spots.

Hornet

Freelance Designer

August 2014 - August 2014 (1 month)

New York, NY

**Method Studios** 

Freelance Designer

August 2014 - August 2014 (1 month)

New York, NY

loyalkaspar

Freelance Designer

March 2014 - July 2014 (5 months)

New York, NY

Created print/web designs and style frames for a wide range of projects including ESPN College Football and CNN The Sixties.

**MPC** 

Motion Designer June 2013 - March 2014 (10 months) New York

Mirada Studios Design Intern May 2012 - August 2012 (4 months)

### Education

Art Center College of Design

Bachelor of Illustration, motion design · (2008 - 2013)